<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RCSC Fitness Centre</title>
    <description>RCSC will provide a large, spacious training area, surrounded by a range of core and functional training equipment.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 22:28:49 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 22:28:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.5</generator>
    
      
      <item>
        <title>A big year for RCSC Fitness</title>
        <description>&lt;p class=&quot;intro&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;dropcap&quot;&gt;F&lt;/span&gt;irst we would like to take this opportunity to wish everyone a happy 2020 from all at RCSC Fitness. Fitness usually ends up on a new year's resolutions list and opening a new alternative, low-cost fitness centre in 2020 is top of ours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Me and Rob both compete in Karate, with Rob being my Sensei, owner of the Karate club as well as my sparring partner. Like many other sports, as well as learning the techniques you need a range of physical and functional attributes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Traditional gyms are dominated by cardio and strength machines, often leaving a small space in the corner for free training. With the rapid rise of functional fitness, stretching and sports conditioning, RCSC will provide a large, spacious training area, surrounded by a range of core and functional training equipment.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/touring.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have worked on the concept throughout 2019 and are now ready to setup our new sports conditioning centre for the towns of Cleethorpes and Grimsby during 2020. It’s going to be a big year for RCSC Fitness so please &lt;a href=&quot;/subscribe&quot;&gt;subscribe to our mailing list for updates and offers.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
          <description>&lt;p class=&quot;intro&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;dropcap&quot;&gt;F&lt;/span&gt;irst we would like to take this opportunity to wish everyone a happy 2020 from all at RCSC Fitness. Fitness usually ends up on a new year's resolutions list and opening a new alternative, low-cost fitness centre in 2020 is top of ours.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/updates/happy-new-year/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/updates/happy-new-year/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>
